<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Woman calendar</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_articles">Articles</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>
    <string name="period_in">Period in</string>
    <string name="log_period">Log period</string>
    <string name="my_daily_insights">My daily insights</string>
    <string name="log_your_symptoms">Log your symptoms</string>
    <string name="my_cycle">My cycle</string>
    <string name="current_cycle_nn_days">Current cycle: %s days</string>
    <string name="nn_days">%s days</string>
    <string name="nn_day">%s day</string>
    <string name="month_dd_month_dd">%s %s - %s %s</string>
    <string name="started_month_dd_yyyy">Started %s %s, %s</string>
    <string name="log_previous_cycles">Log previous cycles</string>
    <string name="there_are_no_data_to_analyze_and_compare_yet">There are no data to analyze and compare yet</string>
    <string name="log_at_least_2_periods_to_get_personalized_insights_about_your_previous_cycle_and_period_length">Log at least 2 periods to get personalized insights about your previous cycle and period length</string>
    <string name="log_at_least_3_periods_to_get_insights_about_your_cycle_regularity">Log at least 3 periods to get insights about your cycle regularity</string>
    <string name="log_previous_cycle">Log previous cycle</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="dates_are_auto_filled_tap_them_to_adjust">Dates are auto-filled. Tap them to adjust.</string>
    <string name="contin">Continue</string>
    <string name="period">Period</string>
    <string name="ovulation_in">Ovulation in</string>
    <string name="edit_period_dates">Edit period dates</string>
    <string name="period_may_start_today">Period may start today</string>
    <string name="current_cycle">Current cycle</string>
    <string name="dd_month">%s %s</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="edit">edit</string>
    <string name="water">Water</string>
    <string name="sex_and_sex_drive">Sex and sex drive</string>
    <string name="mood">Mood</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="vaginal_discharge">Vaginal Discharge</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="notes">Notes</string>
    <string name="cycle_day_s">Cycle day %s</string>
    <string name="calm">Calm</string>
    <string name="menstrual_flow">Menstrual flow</string>
    <string name="consumed_this_day">Consumed this day</string>
    <string name="volume_of_water">%.2f / %.2f L</string>
    <string name="water_l">%.2f L</string>
    <string name="logged_weight">Logged Weight</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="s_kg">%s kg</string>
    <string name="kg">kg</string>
    <string name="__kg">-- kg</string>
    <string name="__l">-- L</string>
    <string name="discover">Discover</string>
    <string name="reproductive_health">Reproductive Health</string>
    <string name="sex">Sex</string>
    <string name="your_cycle_phase_luteal">Your Cycle Phase: Luteal</string>
    <string name="the_latest">The Latest</string>
    <string name="lgbtq">LGBTQ+</string>
    <string name="trips_for_a_pain_free_cycle">Trips for a Pain-Free Cycle</string>
    <string name="nutrition_and_fitness">Nutrition and Fitness</string>
    <string name="early_sights_of_pregnancy_content">Waiting for your period and puzzled if what you\'re feeling is pregnancy signs or just PMS? Not sure how and when to do a pregnancy test? Wondering if your birth control has you covered or you need a backup plan? Freaking out about getting pregnant so much you\'d rather avoid sex at all? Read on to get the answers!</string>
    <string name="text">Text</string>
    <string name="text_long">Waiting for your period and puzzled if what you\'re feeling is pregnancy signs or just PMS? Not sure how and when to do a pregnancy test? Wondering if your birth control has you covered or you need a backup plan? Freaking out about getting pregnant so much you\'d rather avoid sex at all? Read on to get the answers!</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="today_is_n_your_cycle_day_s">Today is\n Your Cycle Day %s</string>
    <string name="the_prediction_is_based_on_the_last_period_n_you_logged">The prediction is based on the last period\n you logged</string>
    <string name="month_dd_cycle_day_nn">%s %d, Cycle day %s</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_today">Hormones and body today</string>
    <string name="in_the_latter_part_of_your_period">In the latter part of your period, progesterone is low but estrogen starts rising, which may give energy levels a boost</string>
    <string name="today_s_wins">Today’s wins</string>
    <string name="today_s_challenges">Today’s challenges</string>

    <string name="hormones_and_body_post_period">You may experience a surge in estrogen-based energy and productivity, though there is a risk of overdoing things</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_period_start">Your progesterone and estrogen levels are low but stable - though you may lack energy, your mood should feel steady</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_period_mid">After ovulation, estrogen falls and progesterone rises, so you may feel calmer, but lacking energy</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_period_end">In the latter part of your period, progesterone is low but estrogen starts rising, which may give energy levels a boost</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_pre_period_start">After ovulation, estrogen falls and progesterone rises, so you may feel calmer, but lacking energy</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_pre_period_mid">After ovulation, estrogen falls and progesterone rises, so you may feel calmer, but lacking energy</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_pre_period_end">After ovulation, estrogen falls and progesterone rises, so you may feel calmer, but lacking energy</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_post_fertile_start">With estrogen and progesterone up, your sense of direction and coordination are up in the luteal phase, but you may experience oilyskin</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_post_fertile_mid">With estrogen and progesterone up, your sense of direction and coordination are up in the luteal phase, but you may experience oilyskin</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_post_fertile_end">At the end of the luteal phase, with rising estrogen and progesterone, you may have all the feels, but stress can be a big one Today</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_fertile_start">With estrogen and progesterone up, your sense of direction and coordination are up in the luteal phase, but you may experience oilyskin</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_ovulation_day">With estrogen and progesterone up, your sense of direction and coordination are up in the luteal phase, but you may experience oilyskin</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_fertile_mid">With estrogen and progesterone up, your sense of direction and coordination are up in the luteal phase, but you may experience oilyskin</string>
    <string name="hormones_and_body_fertile_end">With estrogen and progesterone up, your sense of direction and coordination are up in the luteal phase, but you may experience oilyskin</string>

    <string name="greater_stamina">Greater stamina</string>
    <string name="greater_stamina_content">As estrogen rises, your body may shift from finite glycogen (carbohydrates) to fat as an
energy source - now\'s the time to wow your family or friends with a dinner or cocktail party</string>
    <string name="increased_productivity">Increased productivity</string>
    <string name="increased_productivity_content">Rising levels of estrogen may improve working memory - used during reasoning, learning, and comprehension-based activities.
This is a good day for learning a couple of new words</string>
    <string name="overdoing_things">Overdoing things</string>
    <string name="overdoing_things_content">Though you may be enjoying increased energy and reward-based motivation due to
rising estrogen levels, try to pace yourself. Take a time-out with a mind-clearing walk outdoors</string>
    <string name="sensitive_hearing">Sensitive hearing</string>
    <string name="sensitive_hearing_content">Estrogen is linked with hearing, and rising levels at this time may cause increased audio sensitivity. Be mindful if you\'re going to loud
places like concerts or nightclubs</string>
    <string name="breast_comfort">Breast comfort</string>
    <string name="breast_comfort_content">Breast tenderness, caused by pre-period hormonal drop, has eased, making going for
a walk, swimming, or cycling more pleasant</string>
    <string name="better_digestion">Better digestion</string>
    <string name="better_digestion_content">If you\'ve been suffering from bloating or diarrhea, these symptoms should ease up now that prostaglandin activity (a key trigger)
is in decline. Celebrate with some tasty takeout</string>
    <string name="disrupted_sleep">Disrupted sleep</string>
    <string name="disrupted_sleep_content">Progesterone is linked to sleep, so low levels may mean you find it harder to fall asleep. Stop screen use an hour before bed and try
a simple meditation</string>
    <string name="low_mood">Low mood</string>
    <string name="low_mood_content">Although estrogen is rising, it\'s still relatively low, restricting production of serotonin (AKA the happy hormone). Try a positive, mindful
activity like gratitude journaling</string>
    <string name="zen_vibes">Zen vibes</string>
    <string name="zen_vibes_content">With hormones low but stable, this is
a comparatively calmer time, so you may feel more able to concentrate. This is a good time
to return to more complex work projects</string>
    <string name="battery_recharging">Battery recharging</string>
    <string name="battery_recharging_content">With symptoms from bleeding to cramping still going on and low estrogen affecting energy levels, try activities that help you rest and relax, such as mindful meditation</string>
    <string name="tricky_skin">Tricky skin</string>
    <string name="tricky_skin_content">Low estrogen levels can affect the skin, resulting in excessive sebum production that blocks pores and causes breakouts. Try
a deep cleansing treatment like a charcoal face mask</string>
    <string name="period_pain">Period pain</string>
    <string name="period_pain_content">You may still be experiencing cramps and back pain due to the release of prostaglandins. Try a simple yoga pose, such as child\'s pose or seated cat-cow</string>
    <string name="speedy_scanning">Speedy scanning</string>
    <string name="speedy_scanning_content">Due to falling progesterone and estrogen, the late luteal phase is linked to higher perceptual speed when comparing/scanning figures
today\'s the day to crush that spreadsheet</string>
    <string name="winning_words">Winning words</string>
    <string name="winning_words_content">As levels of estrogen and progesterone decline, you may find verbal fluency increases, making you more articulate. Channel this into creative writing or blogging</string>
    <string name="pre_period_pain">Pre-period pain</string>
    <string name="pre_period_pain_content">Before your period, you may experience cramps caused by prostaglandins, which make the muscles in the uterus contract.
Putting a heat pad on your stomach can help</string>
    <string name="easy_orientation">Easy orientation</string>
    <string name="easy_orientation_content">Spatial navigation improves due to declining estrogen and progesterone levels, meaning you may find map-reading and orientation easier. A good day to go for a hike somewhere new</string>
    <string name="emotional_intelligence">Emotional intelligence</string>
    <string name="emotional_intelligence_content">Though progesterone is falling, relatively high levels are linked to emotional perceptiveness. Tackle relationship conflicts while you\'re in your prime</string>
    <string name="water_retention">Water retention</string>
    <string name="water_retention_content">As progesterone falls, you may experience bloating, which can impact digestion. Try to avoid salty foods and stay hydrated</string>
    <string name="breast_discomfort">Breast discomfort</string>
    <string name="breast_discomfort_content">Fluctuations in estrogen and progesterone may trigger breast pain, so it may be a good day to opt for looser, more comfortable tops (though a supportive bra is a must)</string>
    <string name="emotional_intelligence_content_post_fertile">Due to rising estrogen, emotional awareness and sensitivity to others\' reactions may increase, especially sadness. Reach out to loved ones who may be in need</string>
    <string name="extra_empathy">Extra empathy</string>
    <string name="extra_empathy_content">Increased understanding of negative emotions is linked to the luteal phase, so this could be a good day to tackle thorny conversations with colleagues or managers</string>
    <string name="oily_skin">Oily skin</string>
    <string name="oily_skin_content">High progesterone is linked to sebum production, so your skin may look greasier. Use a cleansing brush at night to deep clean your skin before using a light moisturizer</string>
    <string name="low_mood_content_post_fertile">High levels of progesterone can increase amygdala reactivity in the brain, which can trigger feelings of stress. Try a guided meditation before bed to help you let go of
any worries</string>
    <string name="easy_orientation_content_post_fertile">Increased progesterone boosts spatial navigation, meaning you may find it easier to navigate journeys. Volunteer to helm a road
trip with friends</string>
    <string name="smooth_moves">Smooth moves</string>
    <string name="smooth_moves_content">As estrogen and progesterone rise, you may find your fine motor coordination improves, making this the perfect time for a dance class</string>
    <string name="feeling_sweaty">Feeling sweaty</string>
    <string name="feeling_sweaty_content">As progesterone rises, basal body temperature increases, so you may sweat more. Opt for lighter clothing options in natural fibers to feel more comfortable</string>
    <string name="less_swelling">Less swelling</string>
    <string name="less_swelling_content">Estrogen is linked to water retention, which can cause swollen fingers and puffy ankles
- as it falls, you may find swelling eases off. You can safely wear your favorite heels or
sandals</string>
    <string name="emotional_intelligence_content_fertile">Falling estrogen levels may be linked to greater emotional awareness and sensitivity in terms of perceiving others\' reactions and feelings a good day to help those in need</string>
    <string name="major_munchies">Major munchies</string>
    <string name="major_munchies_content">Rising levels of progesterone have been linked to increased appetite and the desire for sugar and fat-rich foods. Try to fill up on
healthy veggies with a big salad</string>
    <string name="energy_loss">Energy loss</string>
    <string name="energy_loss_content">Estrogen - linked to more efficient energy metabolism - is falling, so you may find you are fatigued sooner. Opt for moderate exercise like a shorter-than-normal jog</string>

    <string name="notification_post_period_1">You might feel friskier today. What else to expect? Tap to see</string>
    <string name="notification_post_period_2">You can expect bloating and acne among other things. See why</string>
    <string name="notification_period_end">You may have a headache today. What else to expect? Tap to see</string>
    <string name="notification_period_mid">You may feel bloated today. What else to expect? Tap to see</string>
    <string name="notification_period_start">Your breasts may be extra sensitive today. What else to expect? Tap to see</string>
    <string name="notification_pre_period_end">Bloating is common today. What are your symptoms? Log now to get expert tips</string>
    <string name="notification_pre_period_mid">A backache could occur at this time. What do you feel? Log your symptoms to get tips</string>
    <string name="notification_pre_period_start">Breast sensitivity is common today. What do you feel? Log your symptoms to get tips</string>
    <string name="notification_post_fertile_end">You might notice a headache today. What else to expect? Tap to see</string>
    <string name="notification_post_fertile_start_mid">You may notice increased appetite among other things. See what else to expect</string>
    <string name="notification_fertile">You might notice bloating today. What else to expect? Tap to see 👉</string>
    <string name="notification_ovulation_day">Your most fertile days are today! You might notice bloating today. What else to expect? Tap to see 👉</string>

</resources>